<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Care Tracker</string>

    <!--TASKS GENERATED BY CHATGPT 3.5 -->
    <string name="task_title_1">Prepare a Delicious Dinner</string>
    <string name="task_desc_1">You\'re tasked with preparing a delicious dinner for your family or friends. This involves planning a well-balanced menu, shopping for fresh ingredients, and executing the cooking process. Whether you\'re an experienced chef or a novice cook, crafting a memorable meal involves creativity and precision. You\'ll have to follow recipes, chop, sauté, bake, and season your dishes to perfection. At the end of this culinary adventure, the reward is not just a full stomach but also the satisfaction of creating a delightful dining experience for your loved ones.</string>

    <string name="task_title_2">Organize a Charity Event</string>
    <string name="task_desc_2">Your task is to organize a charity event to support a noble cause. This involves planning logistics, coordinating volunteers, securing sponsors, and promoting the event. Whether it\'s a fundraising gala, a charity run, or a community outreach program, your efforts will make a meaningful impact on those in need.</string>

    <string name="task_title_3">Complete a Home Renovation</string>
    <string name="task_desc_3">You\'re tasked with completing a home renovation project. This involves making design decisions, hiring contractors, overseeing construction, and ensuring the project stays within budget and timeline. Whether it\'s remodeling a kitchen, renovating a bathroom, or upgrading the entire home, your attention to detail and project management skills will transform your living space.</string>

    <string name="task_title_4">Write a Compelling Short Story</string>
    <string name="task_desc_4">Your task is to write a compelling short story that captivates readers. This involves brainstorming ideas, developing characters, creating a plot, and crafting engaging prose. Whether it\'s a thrilling mystery, a heartwarming romance, or a thought-provoking drama, your storytelling skills will transport readers to new worlds and emotions.</string>

    <string name="task_title_5">Plan a Cross-Country Road Trip</string>
    <string name="task_desc_5">Tasked with planning a cross-country road trip, you\'ll embark on an adventure of a lifetime. This involves selecting destinations, mapping routes, booking accommodations, and creating a memorable itinerary. Whether it\'s exploring national parks, experiencing diverse cultures, or savoring local cuisine, your road trip planning will lead to unforgettable experiences and lasting memories.</string>

    <string name="task_title_6">Start a Personal Fitness Challenge</string>
    <string name="task_desc_6">Starting a personal fitness challenge is your task to improve your health and well-being. This involves setting fitness goals, creating a workout plan, tracking progress, and making healthy dietary choices. Whether it\'s increasing endurance, building strength, or losing weight, your commitment to this challenge will lead to improved physical and mental fitness.</string>

    <string name="task_title_7">Design a Custom Website</string>
    <string name="task_desc_7">Your task is to design a custom website that meets the needs and vision of your client. This involves gathering requirements, creating wireframes, choosing a design aesthetic, and developing web pages. Whether it\'s a business website, an e-commerce platform, or a personal blog, your web design skills will bring digital concepts to life.</string>

</resources>